You look cute in bubbles.
你全身泡泡好可愛
You're just all liquored up.
你喝太多眼花了
Hey,it's me. I'm coming in.
是我，我進去了
I've had a very long,hard day.
我今天上班累死了
-You're home early. -Yeah,my date threw up.
你提早回家 因為我約會對像吐了一地
Want some chicken?
我要去買炸雞，你要不要？
No,thanks. No chicken. Bye-bye.
不了，謝謝，再見
You sure? Some extra-crispy,dirty rice?
你確定？炸雞喔？ 不要海鮮飯或豆子？
For the last time,no! Get out,Joey!
我最後一次說我不要了 出去，喬伊
All right.
知道了
Are you okay? He wouldn't leave.
你沒事吧？抱歉，他死都不走
He kept asking me if I wanted chicken.
纏著我問要不要炸雞
Chicken?
炸雞？
I could eat some chicken.
我想吃炸雞
喬伊
Could I get a three-piece, some coleslaw,some beans and a Coke?
我要三塊雞、沙拉 豆子、可樂
Diet Coke.
健怡可樂
The One With All the Kissing
本集播出：「熱吻連連」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
-Morning,Phoebe. -I have to tell you this story.
早安，菲比  我非告訴你們不可
I was coming over and this cabdriver
剛才載我來的司機…
Was his name Angus?
那人是不是叫做安格斯？
What?
什麼？
He was a cabdriver we had in London.
我們在倫敦碰到的計程車司機
All right. Anyway
好吧，總之…
What was that pub he took us to?
他載我們去的酒館叫什麼？
The Wheat Sheaf!
麥子酒館
And they had that beer....
對，那裡有一種啤酒…
Boddington's!
柏丁頓
Phoebe was going to tell a story.
菲比有話要說
So he had a really funny hat.
他的帽子很好笑…
I don't want to talk about it.
我不想說了
-Hey. -Hey,Ross!
羅斯
Boddington's!
柏丁頓
Oh,man!
是啊
I'd walk back to London for another frosty one of those bad boys.
那啤酒真好喝 若是能再喝一杯 要我走回倫敦都行
They have them at the British pub by the Trade Center.
世貿附近的英國酒館好像有
Later!
回頭見
Shouldn't Rachel be back?
瑞秋不是應該回來了嗎？
Her plane got delayed.
可是班機在雅典誤點
But she should be here by now.
不過現在也該到了
So you talked to her? Did she sound mad?
你跟她通過電話 她很生氣嗎？
No. But she likes me.
不會，那是因為她喜歡我
You abandoned her on a plane to Greece.
你丟她獨自飛到希臘去
I did not "abandon" Rachel. Okay?
我才沒有丟下瑞秋
Emily showed up at the airport.
艾蜜莉出現在機場
I had to go after her. I did what I had to do.
我當然得去追她 我別無選擇
She's my wife. Rachel is my wife.
畢竟瑞秋是我太太
Emily!
是…艾蜜莉
Emily is my wife.
艾蜜莉是我老婆
Man,what is that?
我是怎麼了？
You haven't heard from Emily?
你還沒有艾蜜莉的消息？
Not since I lost her at the airport.
我在機場追丟之後就沒有了
I can't believe she can outrun you.
她竟然跑得比你快
Hey! She's fast,okay?
她是飛毛腿，好嗎？
You think you can beat me? Let's go! Outside!
你自以為能打敗我？ 我們現在就去外頭較量
-I'm sorry. I'm just a little -Slow?
抱歉，我太… 慢了？
Oh,you want some?!
你要跟我比？
Okay,get the shoes on! Let's go,man!
走啊，去穿球鞋，我們去賽跑
It's cool,okay?
別激動
You're the fastest!
你跑得最快
-Hi! -Oh,my God,Rachel!
嗨 瑞秋 嗨
Rach,I am so sorry. I am so,so sorry.
瑞秋，我很抱歉 非常對不起你
Come on. You just did what you had to do.
羅斯，你沒做錯
嗨，菲比
That's it? You're not mad? It must've been terrible.
就這樣？你不生氣？ 你應該很火大
Terrible? Hell,I was in Greece!
火大？我可是在希臘
There was a nice hotel,nice beach, met the nice people.
那間飯店非常棒 海灘很美，人又和善
It's not too shabby for Rachel.
對我瑞秋來說可不差
So,what,that's it?
就這樣？不生氣？
We're cool. Totally cool.
對，我沒生你的氣
Thanks,Rach. You're the best.
謝謝，你真好
Oh,no. You're the best.
你才好呢
Oh,I got to go to the flower store.
我要去花店一趟
No one will tell me where Emily is...
聽我說，大家都不肯說 艾蜜莉在哪裡
...so I'm sending 72 long-stemmed,red roses to her parents' house.
我決定買72朵長莖紅玫瑰 送去艾蜜莉爸媽家
One for each day I've known and loved her.
每朵代表我認識她 並且深愛她的每一天
That should get her talking.
她一定會感動地軟化
When you make out the card, be sure to make it out to "Emily."
羅斯，寫卡片時別忘了 對方是「艾蜜莉」
It's good that you had such a good time in Greece.
瑞秋，太好了 幸好你在希臘玩得開心
What?
什麼？
I didn't have a good time in Greece!
我在希臘才不開心
Ross abandoned me!
羅斯丟下我一人
I couldn't get a plane out. I had to stay in their suite!
我買不到機票回來 只好住在他們的蜜月套房
People came up to me going, "Mrs. Geller! Why are you cry?"
每個人都要來問我 「蓋勒太太，你哭什麼？」
I mean,it was so humiliating!
簡直丟死人了
I felt like such an idiot!
我真是個白癡
It's all my fault. You know why?
這都是我的錯 你們知道為什麼嗎？
Because I make very bad decisions.
因為我的決定都不對
Oh,that's not true.
不要這麼說
Yes,it is true. I went after Ross in stupid London!
就是這樣，我沒胡說 我跑去蠢倫敦追羅斯
London is stupid! Stupid!
倫敦的確是個蠢地方
I put on a cheerleading outfit to seduce Joshua.
打扮得像個啦啦隊長 倒追約書亞
Then I lost him because I asked him to marry me after four dates.
約了四次會就叫他娶我 把他嚇死了
And then I went to Greece on somebody else's honeymoon. Okay?
然後我還去希臘渡別人的蜜月
Do those sound like very good decisions to you?
你們覺得這些決定正確嗎？
I like your little braid.
你的辮子很可愛
I just shouldn't be allowed to make decisions anymore.
我不應該做任何決定
Phoebe,you were right. I should've never gone to London.
菲比，你說得對 我根本不該去倫敦
From now on,you make all my decisions for me.
從今開始由你幫我做決定
Oh,no. I did that for someone once.
不行，我以前就這麼做過
I'm not comfortable having that power over someone's life.
我不喜歡主宰別人的生活
I'll do it.
那我來
Fine. Monica,you are now in charge of my love life.
很好，摩妮卡 以後由你主宰我的感情生活
Okay. I got to go to work.
我該去上班了
And Rachel,great to have you back.
瑞秋，很高興看到你回來
菲比
Always a pleasure.
看到你真開心
Rachel? Sweetie,look.
瑞秋，你看
Here's a cute picture of you and Joey.
這是你跟喬伊在招待會的照片
He's married.
他已經結婚了
Ross is married. I still can't believe it.
羅斯結婚了 我到現在還不敢相信
Honey,sweetie,by the edges.
親愛的，抓旁邊就好
I'll just have to accept it.
看來我只好接受事實
I mean,it's my fault.
這都要怪我
Edges! Fingers! Smudgy!
別抓中間，指紋會弄髒照片
Oh,my God!
天啊
That's okay. I know that you're very upset right now.
算了 我知道你心情低落
I know that wasn't about me.
不是故意找我麻煩
I bet it was about her a little.
我看她就是跟她作對
If you'd stop thinking about Ross...
你要是肯放下羅斯一分鐘
...you'd notice there are great guys everywhere.
就會發現到處有帥哥
Look. Gunther.
你看，例如阿甘
He's nice. He's cute.
他既善良又可愛
Yeah. I guess Gunther is....
阿甘的確…
What about that guy over there?
還有那邊那個傢伙
That's the guy you flirted with at the counter.
記得嗎？你以前 跟他打情罵俏過
-Oh,I don't know. I don't know. -You're going to talk to him.
我不知道… 我不知道 你現在就去跟他說話
I make your decisions, and I say you're going to talk to him.
我們說好由我發號施令 我命令你去跟他說話
All right.
好吧
You're the boss. I got to do what you tell me.
你說了算 看來我只好照辦
Say that to him,and you're golden.
他聽到這句話肯定上鉤
嘿 嗨
Hey,Phoebe. We got our pictures back from London.
菲比 倫敦的照片洗出來了
Here's all of us at the Tower of London....
這張是所有人在倫敦塔拍的
Here we all are.
大家都在照片中
There's Ross and Joey and you and
有羅斯、喬伊、你…
And me.
和我
We've been talking about London too much.
你一定聽煩我們說倫敦的事了
Sorry,it's just because I couldn't be there.
是我不好，因為我去不了
All I get to do now is pregnant stuff. It bums me out.
我只能大著肚子 煩都快煩死了
-I'm sorry. -Sorry.
可憐啊…
Know what I like to do? It sounds a little corny...
你知道我傷心時都怎麼做嗎？
...but sometimes when I'm bummed out, I like to just close my eyes...
有時候事情不太順利 我就閉上眼睛
...and think about what a wonderful gift life is.
想想人生實在挺美好
See?
有用吧？
-What happened? -A little of this,a little of that.
怎麼樣？總之我們東扯西扯
I got myself a date tomorrow.
明天晚上要出去約會
See? Didn't I tell you? You're getting over Ross already.
看吧？你就要忘記羅斯了
Get out.
滾出去 「我們有權利拒絕服務」
What took so long?
你怎麼去那麼久？
I got caught up at work. But I'm quitting tomorrow.
公事擔擱了 不過我明天就辭職
So thanks for having me over.
謝謝你邀我過來
瑞秋
菲比
See you,man.
再見
What the hell was that?
他發什麼神經？
Probably some European goodbye thing he picked up in London.
可能在倫敦學到的歐洲風俗
That's not European.
那才不是歐洲風俗
It felt French.
比較像法式熱吻
Well,I guess it's time for me to say goodbye too,mon frere.
換我跟各位老友說再見了
Come here and give me a little sugar.
過來給我一個熱吻吧
I really had a good time.
我玩得好開心
Yeah,me too.
我也是
I guess this is it.
看來今天要結束了
Unless you want to come inside?
除非你想進來 好
Wait a minute. You know what? I can't decide this.
等等，我無法自做主張
Okay. Just hold on a second.
等我一下 好
Where's Monica? I have to ask her something.
摩妮卡在嗎？我有事要問她
Doing her laundry.
她去洗衣服
What's that?
那是什麼？
It came in the mail today.
我今天收到的包裹
It's 72 long-stemmed red roses.
72朵代表...
One for each day I've known and loved Emily...
...我深愛艾蜜莉的紅玫瑰...
...cut up into mulch.
...給剪成碎片
Honey,that's awful.
真是糟糕
It's not so bad.
還好啦
Monica's going to make potpourri.
摩妮卡要用來做香料
I think I'm going to go wander out in the rain for a while.
我要去淋雨散散心
It's not raining.
外面沒下雨
I can't catch a break!
連老天都不賞臉
You're not going anywhere. Sit right here.
羅斯，你哪也別去 就坐這裡
I'll make you some tea and we'll talk this out.
我們喝茶聊天
All right?
好嗎？
Hey,Dave.
大衛 怎麼樣？
I need to take a rain check. My roommate is really sick.
改天再請你進來 我的室友病得很重
Okay. Bye!
再見
Honey,listen.
I know things seem so bad...
我知道你現在...
...and that they won't get any
...一定很傷心
Could I talk to you?
我可以跟你談談嗎？
I dropped some socks.
我掉了幾支襪子
好
What is the matter with you? Do you want to fall into the trap?
你哪根筋不對？ 你又想老調重彈？ 又想跳回去自找苦吃？
You did not drop any socks!
你根本沒掉襪子
I saw Dave,and he said you blew him off!
我剛碰到大衛 他說你打發他走
You listen to me!
你給我聽好
I'm calling the shots! I say you leave Ross and go get Dave.
這裡由我當家 我要你離開羅斯去追大衛
What are you doing?
你到底想怎麼樣？
Well,ultimately I was trying, you know,I wanted...
其實我想…我打算…
...to tell him that I'm still in love with him.
告訴他我還愛他
What? You cannot tell him that!
什麼？你不准說
Why? Why not?
為什麼？
People love to hear that!
大家都喜歡聽到這種話
Come on,I love you.
我愛你
-Wasn't that nice? -No.
你不喜歡聽嗎？
I make the decisions and I say no!
這裡由我做決定， 我不准你說
You know what? No,you don't make my decisions,because...
你不能幫我做決定 因為...
...you're fired.
...我要開除你
You can't fire me.
你不能開除我
I make your decisions, and I say I'm not fired! Ha!
你的事情由我來決定 我說：我沒被開除
Well....
既然如此…
Come on,let me in!
瑞秋，讓我進去
Having some trouble?
怎麼了？
Rachel locked the door.
瑞秋把我鎖在門外
I'll kick that door in if you give me some sugar.
你肯親我，我就幫你撞開
Ross,there's something I wanna talk to you about.
羅斯，我有話要告訴你
-I just need to -Rachel,open this door!
開門！
-What,is it locked? -She's fine. Listen....
門鎖著嗎？ 別管她，聽我說
Rachel,I can do this all night if I have to!
我可以在外面鬼叫一整晚
-You want me to get that? -No. Just let her do her thing...
要不要我去開門？ 別理她
...and we'll do our thing. Because I really need to tell you
我們說我們的 我要告訴你…
Thank you.
謝謝
Rachel? Can I talk to you outside for a sec?
瑞秋，我可以跟你談談嗎？
不可以
We really need to talk.
我真的有話要跟你說
Well,then talk.
那就說啊
Okay,I will.
那我就說咯
Remember that thing we just discussed that you wanted to do?
記得我們剛說你要做的事嗎？
What thing?
什麼事？
Rachel wants to take swing dance lessons.
瑞秋要去學搖擺舞
Which I think is a really stupid idea.
我非常不贊成
It's dangerous. She won't get what she wants.
因為這種舞很危險 她一定學不會
And who knows who she might end up hurting?
而且搞不好還會撞傷人
Monica's right. Swing dancing can be tricky.
摩妮卡說得對 搖擺舞有點危險
I have to use the phone.
我要打電話
I gotta cancel those five giant teddy bears I sent to Emily.
取消五支送給艾蜜莉的熊寶寶
My God! Think of the massacre.
否則熊寶寶難逃死劫
I'm going to do it.
我就是要說
I know you think I'm crazy.
瑞秋，我知道你認為我瘋了
But before you tell him, try to find one person...
但是在你告訴他之前 至少找到一個人...
...who thinks it's a good idea. I bet you can't.
...支持你 我打賭你找不到
Please?
可是… 拜託
All right. Fine.
好吧
Joey! I'm in!
喬伊，我已經進來了
All right. Good deal.
那敢情好
-Hi. -Hey,Rach.
瑞秋
-Did you find anyone who agrees with you? -No.
瑞秋，你找到誰支持你了嗎？ 還沒
But you know what? I think I need a male point of view.
我決定問男性的意見
Joey.
喬伊
-You're a man. -You got that right.
你是男人 貨真價實
Do you think it would be a good idea if I told Ross that I was still in love with him?
你覺得我該告訴羅斯 我還愛他嗎？
Nope.
不
-Phoebe! -Hey,Phoebe.
菲比
-Phoebe? -Yeah.
菲比 怎樣？
You know how you were saying you didn't get to go to London...
你上次說你都不能去倫敦
...and you were feeling left out?
覺得自己遭大家遺棄
Well,we all felt really bad about that...
我們很愧疚
...so we decided to take a little trip together!
決定大家一起去旅行
Oh,that's so nice!
太好了
How great! Where's the trip?
要去哪裡？…
Well,we thought we would all go to a picnic...
我們可以一起去野餐
...in Central Park!
就去中央公園
Central Park?
中央…公園
All of us. All day.
對，大家一起去個一整天
That sucks!
什麼鳥地方？！
That's not a trip! I just came from there.
那根本不算旅行 我才剛從公園過來
What'll we high-five about at the stupid park?
大家去中央公園有什麼好興奮
It's right by my house. All right!
「好耶，就在我家旁邊」
I'm going home to bask in the triumph of my Central Park idea.
我決定回家反省這個爛主意
Hold on a sec there,Mr. Kissy.
等一下，熱吻先生
I wanted to talk to you about...
我一直想跟你討論
...this whole new European thing you've got going on.
你新學的歐洲民情
And I need to say it makes me very uncomfortable...
你搞得我非常不自在
...and I just,you know,just stop it!
拜託你別再親了
Just bringing some culture to the group.
我只是想 介紹大家認識歐洲文化
That's fine. Just don't bring it in my mouth.
只要不要介紹到我嘴裡就好了
It makes me want to puke.
我都快吐了
Hey,everybody! Phoebe is here!
各位，菲比來了
菲比
-Phoebe! Woo! -Okay. Woo! Hi!
菲比 大家好
Phoebe,we decided that the picnic idea was a little....
我們認為野餐的主意…
It didn't have any.... Well,it blew.
實在爛透了
We thought that this afternoon we'd all go away for the whole weekend...
所以今天下午決定
...to Atlantic City.
到大西洋城去渡週末
Atlantic City! Oh,that's a great plan! Whose plan was that?
大西洋城，太好了 誰想到的？
Mine!
我
-Wait. It was my plan. -No...
等等，是我提議的 錯
...I said we needed a new plan.
我說我們應該想個新的計劃
And I came up with Atlantic City.
然後我想到要去大西洋城
Which is the new plan.
這就是新的計劃啊
Why don't we all meet upstairs in an hour.
大家一小時後樓上見
I'm going to go pack. I'm going to go pack my ass off.
我要去打包了 我要搖著大屁股好好打包
Well,I think I'm gonna grab some coffee because my ass is already packed.
我去叫杯咖啡 因為我已經搖屁股打包完了
Let's go.
瑞秋，我們走吧
You know what? I'll meet you in a minute.
我等一下再上去找你
Rachel,you didn't find anyone, so you can't tell him.
不行，瑞秋，沒有人支持你 所以你不能說
You know what? That doesn't matter.
無所謂
Do you know how painful it is to tell someone you love them...
你知道對方不能回應你的愛意
...and not have them say it back?
會有多痛苦嗎？
I don't care.
知道，我不在乎
I can't watch.
好吧，可是我看不下去
What you reading?
你在看什麼？
Paper.
報紙
Yeah? What's it about?
上面說了什麼？
Events from around the globe.
世界各地的新聞
是啊
There's something I have to talk to you about.
羅斯，我有件事要告訴你
Everyone's saying I shouldn't.
雖然大家都叫我別說
But I think they're wrong. People can be wrong.
但是他們都錯了 有時候別人就是看不清楚
Once at work...
當然，有一次上班時...
...I thought carbon dating is fossilized
我說放射性碳測定法太老舊…
I'm really trying to tell you something here.
羅斯，我說正經的
Go ahead.
說吧
I think I'm just going to say it.
我這就說了，現在就告訴你
I'm just going to say it.
現在就告訴你
I'm still in love with you,Ross.
我還愛著你，羅斯
I'm not sure what to do with that right now.
我不知道現在該怎麼回答
What? Was that a joke? Because it's mean.
怎麼了？你跟我開玩笑？ 這就太惡劣了
I'm so dead serious!
我很正經
I'm totally serious!
不能再正經了
Why are you laughing?
那你笑什麼？
Because I just heard it!
因為我剛聽到自己的話
I heard it. And it's ridiculous!
我聽到了，而且覺得很荒謬
I mean....
畢竟...
You're married!
你已經結婚
You're married, and it's just ridiculous!
你有老婆，我說這話太可笑
When I said it,I sort of floated up out of my body.
我說話的當兒似乎靈魂出殼
And then I heard myself say it, and then the floating Rachel....
我的靈魂聽到肉身說話
I was like,"You are such an idiot!"
瑞秋的靈魂認為 自己實在很白癡
-Well,I am married. -I know.
我的確已經結婚 我知道
Though I haven't spoken to her since the wedding.
雖然婚禮後就沒跟老婆說過話
I'm sorry. That's not funny.
抱歉，這不好笑
Actually,it kind of is.
其實還蠻好笑的
My wife won't return my calls.
我老婆不回我電話
I don't know where my wife is.
我不知道太太在哪裡
"Hey,Ross! Where's the missus?" "Don't know!"
「羅斯，你老婆呢？」 我也不知道
Oh,God!
天啊
You know what? Could you forget I told you this?
你可以忘記我剛說的話嗎？
Well,I kind of have to.
我不忘記也不行
Because the thing is
因為事實是…
The thing is,you know, that you're married to Emily.
事實就是你已經娶了艾蜜莉
That is what the thing is.
事實正是如此
Oh,God.
天啊
Things won't be weird between us, right? Was that stupid?
羅斯，我們還是好朋友吧
Me telling you that?
我說自己還愛你真是蠢斃了
I'm glad you did.
不會，我很高興你告訴我
If nothing else...
就算日子很順利
...it's always great when someone tells you they love you.
聽到有人說愛你還是很開心
That's what I said!
我早說過了
-Thank you for being so nice. -No. Thank you for....
謝謝你對我這麼好 我才該謝謝你
Thank you.
謝謝你
Oh,God. I'm just glad I didn't give you the cassette I made of all of our songs.
幸好我沒給你 我錄的那卷錄音帶
-What songs? -Oh,you know:
你錄了哪些歌曲？
-"With or Without You."
「有沒有你」
-"Everybody Hurts."
「大家都會受傷」
-"Rhiannon." -Why "Rhiannon"?
「李安娜」 為什麼選這首？
Come on,you remember! In the living room?
你不記得了？ 就是在客廳啊
On Monica's laundry?
在蒙妮卡洗好的衣服上啊
Not me.
那不是我
Really.
不是？
So,what happened?
怎麼樣了？
Well,it was really hard...
我很難說出口
...but I'm glad I did it.
但是幸好我說了
So was I right or wrong?
你做得對嗎？
-Oh,come on,honey,does it really matter? -No.
這種事情無關對錯 是啊
Yes. I need it for my score book.
沒錯 但是我要記在記分簿上
Diary.
我是說日記
-Okay,let's go! -Yeah,Atlantic City!
大家走吧 大西洋城！
Come on!
Atlantic City,baby!
去大西洋城咯
Let's roll some bones. Hey,Joey!
我們去大賭一筆 喬伊
High-five for rolling bones.
賭博萬歲
Phoebe,you're leaking.
菲比，你尿失禁？
Oh,my God! Your water broke!
天啊，你羊水破了
Oh,okay.
Well,don't worry. I call shotgun.
別放在心上，我要坐前座！
等一下
Phoebe,we have to take you to the hospital now.
菲比，我們得送你去醫院
Okay. Well,there's probably one on the way to Atlantic City.
去大西洋城路上應該有醫院
Phoebe,the babies are coming now.
菲比，你快要生了
Honey! High-five! The babies are coming!
擊掌，你要生了！
Remember when my water broke?
等一下，記不記得 我羊水破的那天？
I can't believe Phoebe's going to have her babies!
菲比竟然快生了
I know. It's beautiful and amazing.
我知道，真是太棒了
I can't believe I had to kiss Phoebe and Rachel every time I left the room.
真不敢相信 我竟然每次離開 都得親菲比跟瑞秋
It's too bad they didn't see us having sex.
可惜她們沒看到我們嘿咻
-Do you know anything about women? -No.
你到底了不瞭解女人？不瞭解
-It's all right. -Okay.
算了 好